https://www.peterdavid.net/privacy-policy/

Skip To Content
HomePrivacy Policy
Who we are
Our website address is: https://www.peterdavid.net.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Contact forms
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you visit our login page, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
Who we share your data with
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Your contact information
Additional information
How we protect your data
What data breach procedures we have in place
What third parties we receive data from
What automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user data
Industry regulatory disclosure requirements
Plugin: Defender Pro
Third parties
This site may be using WPMU DEV third-party cloud storage to store backups of its audit logs where personal information is collected.
Additional data
This site creates and stores an activity log that capture the IP address, username, email address and tracks user activity (like when a user makes a comment). Information will be stored locally for 30 days and remotely for 1 year. Information on remote logs cannot be cleared for security purposes.Share this:TweetLike this:Like Loading...
Have you read…?
Read Free Previews! #1 • #2
Buy it now! EPub • Kindle • Nook • Paperback
Buy it now!
Kindle • Nook • EPub
Buy it now!
Kindle • Nook • EPub
Buy it now!
Kindle • Nook • Paperback • EPub
Buy it now!
Kindle • Nook • Paperback • EPub
Archives Archives
Select Month
October 2020
September 2020
August 2020
July 2020
June 2020
Select Category
1  (3,283)
But I Digress…  (577)
Cowboy Pete’s TV Roundup  (110)
Potato Moon  (90)
Stash Wednesday  (21)
Uncategorized  (2)
Useless Stories  (29)
Recent CommentsGlenn Hauman on Final Presidential debateTony on FREAK OUT FRIDAY – October 30, 2020Tom Keller on FREAK OUT FRIDAY – October 30, 2020Sean Martin on FREAK OUT FRIDAY – October 30, 2020Peter David on Final Presidential debatePeter David on FREAK OUT FRIDAY – October 30, 2020Ben on FREAK OUT FRIDAY – October 30, 2020Tom Keller on FREAK OUT FRIDAY – October 30, 2020Glenn Hauman on Final Presidential debateBrian Jordan on FREAK OUT FRIDAY – October 30, 2020
Contributors
No Strings Attached
Friends
Ariel David
Bill Mumy
Bob Greenberger
CBLDF
Christopher Priest
Tony Isabella
Kathleen DavidRTBTCKI Crafty Tuesday on Thursday and other thingsMonday Mental Health Check-In: Tired but for the right reasonsHappy Eighteenth Birthday to My Daughter CarolineAdjusted to EarlyRTBTCKI Did you miss me? Glenn HaumanWhen people say it’s gotten too commercial, think about who saved us all. https://amzn.to/2Iq748ZUntitledUntitledUntitledUntitledI resent…An epiphany about writingGive him a chance…If You Were A Puppy, My SweetThe Luckiest Man On The Face Of The Earth
Scroll up to top
%d bloggers like this:
